{
    "id": "1ac8710e9fb341248b87be14c34edb17",
    "title": "Grammar exercise: passive voice",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "0dea06b7815947f9871cbbf982bd8665",
            "title": "Passive Voice Exercise",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "Nothing about the accident ……………….. to her.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "knew",
                        "was known",
                        "had known"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "…………………. the thief …………………. by the police?",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "Has, caught",
                        "Has, been caught",
                        "Was, been caught"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "My feelings ………………….. by his caustic remarks.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "have hurt",
                        "hurt",
                        "were hurt"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "An order …………………. by me.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "has placed",
                        "has been placed",
                        "placed"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "Nobody ………………….. by her.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "was betrayed",
                        "has been betrayed",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "The animals ………………….. by the poachers.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "hunted",
                        "were hunting",
                        "were being hunted"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "Prizes ………………….. away by the chief guest.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "are giving",
                        "were being gave",
                        "were being given"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "His life ………………….",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "must have saved",
                        "must save",
                        "must be saved"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "She ………………… by grief.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "has overwhelmed",
                        "was overwhelmed",
                        "was overwhelming"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "The patient ………………….. medicine.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "is administering",
                        "is being administered",
                        "has administered"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}